The end of the line is just the beginning.
Bullet Train is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by David Leitch.
Unlucky assassin Ladybug is determined to do his job
peacefully after one too many gigs gone off the rails.
Fate, however, may have other plans, as Ladybug's latest mission puts him on a collision course with lethal
adversaries from around the globe—all with connected, yet conflicting, objectives—on the world's fastest train.
Ladybug, played by Brad Pitt.
Prince, played by Joey King.
Tangerine, played by Aaron Taylor-Johnson.
Lemon, played by Brian Tyree Henry.
Kimura, played by Andrew Koji.
The Elder, played by Hiroyuki Sanada.
Bullet Train is a 2022 American action comedy film directed by
David Leitch, based on the 2010 novel by Kōtarō Isaka.
Centered around a group of assassins on a Japanese high-speed train who end up in conflict with each other, the film features an ensemble cast consisting of
Brad Pitt, Joey King, Aaron Taylor-Johnson, Brian Tyree Henry, Andrew Koji, Hiroyuki Sanada, Michael Shannon, Bad Bunny, and Sandra Bullock.
Principal photography began in Los Angeles in
November 2020 and completed in March 2021.
Bullet Train premiered in Paris on July 18, 2022, and was theatrically released
in the United States on August 5, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed
$239 million on a production budget of $86–90M.
The film explores themes of mission, japan, assassin,
based on novel or book, briefcase.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.